Senate fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
Senate fonds
1964 - 1996
F-84
17 m of textual records
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department Maggie Benston Student Services Building, Rm. 0400 8888 University Dr. Burnaby British Columbia Canada V5A 1S6 Telephone: 778.782.3805 Email: archives@sfu.ca http://www.sfu.ca/archives
Senate
The British Columbia Universities Act of March 1963, which created Simon Fraser University, required the establishment of a University Senate for the management of curriculum, instruction and education. The Act, and its subsequent amendments over the years, specified the membership, duties and powers of the Senate. As of May 2003 Senate is made up of 60 elected and appointed members chosen from faculty, students, staff, convocation, and the community. Senate is responsible for such academic matters as determining requirements for admission; providing for and granting degrees including honorary degrees; recommending to the Board of Governors the establishment or discontinuation of any faculty, department, or course of instruction; awarding fellowships and bursaries; making rules for the management of the library; and providing for the publication of the University calendar.
The President of the University is the chair of the Senate. Senate elects a Vice-Chair annually. The Registrar is the Secretary of Senate according to the University Act, and has delegated to the Director, University Secretariat, the responsibilities for the management of Senate and its committees.
Senate usually meets once a month in open and closed sessions except for August when no meeting is held. Matters for decision are normally brought to Senate through the Senate Committee on Agenda and Rules.
The first meeting of the SFU Senate was held November 29, 1965. In 1967, Senate voted to allow three student representatives--a move hailed as a first for a Canadian university. In 1968, in another precedent-setting decision, Senate admitted observers to its open sessions.
For further information on Senate membership, committees, duties, powers, and rules, see the appendix to this finding aid which contains a print out from the Senate web page, or consult the web page itself for the most current information at http://www.reg.sfu.ca/Senate/
published
Full
Revised
Title of the fonds is based on the name of its creator.
The fonds consists primarily of agendas, minutes and supporting papers from the various committees of Senate. In addition, the fonds contains a series of Registrar's Senate correspondence concerning administrative matters and a series of subject files kept by the Registrar on topics of interest to Senate. Finally, the fonds includes a series of Senate reference files compiled by previous Archives staff for informational purposes. Document types include agendas, minutes, supporting papers, correspondence, terms of reference, reports, briefs, proposals, policies, statistics, lists, publications, handbooks, drafts, notes, working papers and other documents.
Note: The records of the full Senate (agendas, minutes and papers) are held by the Senate Secretariat; a vital records set of agendas, minutes and papers is held in archival storage and is not accessible. Researchers wishing to inspect Senate agendas, minutes and papers should consult the Senate Secretariat.
The files were arranged by the archivist except for Series 84-1, Committees, which mostly followed the order maintained by the Registrar.
The records were transferred to the Archives in several accessions.
Additional material has been accessioned but not yet processed (as of June 2003: 1.33 m., 1972-1999). Please consult the archivist for information about using these materials; restrictions may apply.
The fonds includes records containing personal information. Access to these files is restricted in accordance with the provisions of British Columbia's Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act (RSBC 1996 c. 165). Files marked "pending review" must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release, and as a result of the review some files may be restricted in accordance with the FOI/POP Act. Please see the file lists and consult the archivist for more details.
A file list is available in the hard copy version of the finding aid maintained in the Archives Reading Room.
- Senate Committees, 1965 - 1987; F-84-1; 13.72 m of textual records
  published
  The Senate operates through a system of standing and ad hoc committees. As of 2003, there are 24 Senate committees, but the number of committees has varied over time. Senate determines the membership and method of appointing or electing members to the committees. Most Senate committees have ex-officio administrators as chairs and only a few have Vice-chairs.
  Standing committees with delegated responsibilities to perform duties on behalf of Senate usually report to Senate at yearly intervals. Temporary committees report to Senate by the date stated in the charge to the committee.
  This series consists of records relating to the meetings and activities of the various Senate Committees.
  Records include terms of reference; membership lists; and agendas, minutes, and supporting papers including correspondence, reports, briefs, course proposals, policies, statistics, lists, publications, drafts, notes, working papers and other documents.
  Each committee has been assigned a separate sub-series.
  Records were placed in folders, and, in most cases, kept as maintained by the Registrar in reverse chronological order in binders. In some cases, particularly with ad hoc committees, the archivist provided the arrangement. For the following committees, please consult the archivist for additional notes contained in the "Series Disposition Recommendation and Rationale," in the Collections File: Senate Committee on Examination Grading and Scholastic Standing; Assessment Committee for New Graduate Programs; Senate Committee on Scholarships, Awards and Bursaries; Senate Library Committee; Senate Undergraduate Admissions Board; and Senate Graduate Admissions Board.
  Further accruals to the series are expected.
  Access to files containing personal information may be restricted in accordance with the provisions of British Columbia's Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act (RSBC 1996 c. 165). Files marked "pending review" must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release, and as a result of the review some files may be restricted in accordance with the FOI/POP Act. Please see the file lists and consult the archivist for more details.
  A file list is available.
  - Senate Committee on Academic Planning (SCAP), 1974 - 1987; F-84-1-1; 1.01 m of textual records
    Some files may contain personal or confidential information. Access to these files may be restricted as required by law. Files marked 'pending review' must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release, and as a result of the review access restrictions may apply. Please see the file lists and consult the archivist for more details.
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Apr. 1974 - July 1975, 1974 - 1975; F-84-1-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 84-1)
      Textual records
      Pending review
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Aug. - Sept. 1975, F-84-1-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 84-1)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 26, 1975, F-84-1-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 84-1)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Dec. 10-11, 1975, F-84-1-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 84-1)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Dec. 10-17, 1975, F-84-1-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 84-1)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Jan. 7 - Feb. 18, 1976, F-84-1-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 84-1)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Mar. 3 - Apr. 21, 1976, F-84-1-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 84-1)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Jan. 7 - Apr. 21,1976, F-84-1-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 84-1)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. May 12 - Sept. 29, 1976, F-84-1-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 84-1)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Oct. 27 - Nov. 17, 1976, F-84-1-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 84-2)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Dec. 8, 1976, F-84-1-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 84-2)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Feb. - June 1977, F-84-1-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 84-2)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Sept. 21, 1977, F-84-1-1-0-13 (Archival box - standard 84-2)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 16 - Dec. 21, 1977, F-84-1-1-0-14 (Archival box - standard 84-2)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Jan. 25 - Mar. 22, 1978, F-84-1-1-0-15 (Archival box - standard 84-2)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Apr. 19, 1978, F-84-1-1-0-16 (Archival box - standard 84-2)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. May 10 - Oct. 18, 1978, F-84-1-1-0-17 (Archival box - standard 84-3)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 8, 1978, F-84-1-1-0-18 (Archival box - standard 84-3)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Dec. 6-13, 1978, F-84-1-1-0-19 (Archival box - standard 84-3)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Jan. 10-31, 1979, F-84-1-1-0-20 (Archival box - standard 84-3)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Feb. 7 - Sept. 12, 1979, F-84-1-1-0-21 (Archival box - standard 84-3)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Oct. 3 - Nov. 7, 1979, F-84-1-1-0-22 (Archival box - standard 84-3)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Dec. 5, 1979, F-84-1-1-0-23 (Archival box - standard 84-3)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Dec. 12, 1979, F-84-1-1-0-24 (Archival box - standard 84-3)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Jan. 16 - Mar. 1980, F-84-1-1-0-25 (Archival box - standard 84-3)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Apr. 16 - July 9, 1980, F-84-1-1-0-26 (Archival box - standard 84-4)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Aug. 13 - Oct. 8, 1980, F-84-1-1-0-27 (Archival box - standard 84-4)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Oct. 22, 1980, F-84-1-1-0-28 (Archival box - standard 84-4)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 5 - Dec. 30, 1980, F-84-1-1-0-29 (Archival box - standard 84-4)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Jan. 14 - Feb. 11, 1981, F-84-1-1-0-30 (Archival box - standard 84-4)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Mar. 4 - May 13, 1981, F-84-1-1-0-31 (Archival box - standard 84-4)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. June 10-24, 1981, F-84-1-1-0-32 (Archival box - standard 84-4)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. July 15. 1981, F-84-1-1-0-33 (Archival box - standard 84-5)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Sept. 16, 1981, F-84-1-1-0-34 (Archival box - standard 84-5)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Sept. 30 - Dec. 9, 1981, F-84-1-1-0-35 (Archival box - standard 84-5)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Jan. 13, 1982, F-84-1-1-0-36 (Archival box - standard 84-5)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Feb. 10 - Mar. 3, 1982, F-84-1-1-0-37 (Archival box - standard 84-5)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Apr. 7, 1982, F-84-1-1-0-38 (Archival box - standard 84-5)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. May 12 - June 9, 1982, F-84-1-1-0-39 (Archival box - standard 84-5)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. July - Oct. 1982, F-84-1-1-0-40 (Archival box - standard 84-6)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Dec. 1982, F-84-1-1-0-41 (Archival box - standard 84-6)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Feb. - Apr. 1983, F-84-1-1-0-42 (Archival box - standard 84-6)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. June - July 1983, F-84-1-1-0-43 (Archival box - standard 84-6)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Oct. 1983, F-84-1-1-0-44 (Archival box - standard 84-6)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 1983 - Jan. 1984, 1983 - 1984; F-84-1-1-0-45 (Archival box - standard 84-6)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Feb. - Mar. 1984, F-84-1-1-0-46 (Archival box - standard 84-6)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Apr. 1984, F-84-1-1-0-47 (Archival box - standard 84-7)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. May - Oct. 1984, F-84-1-1-0-48 (Archival box - standard 84-7)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 1984, F-84-1-1-0-49 (Archival box - standard 84-7)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Jan. - Mar. 1985, F-84-1-1-0-50 (Archival box - standard 84-7)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Apr. 1985, F-84-1-1-0-51 (Archival box - standard 84-7)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Oct. 1985 - Jan. 1986, 1985 - 1986; F-84-1-1-0-52 (Archival box - standard 84-7)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Feb. - Apr. 1986, F-84-1-1-0-53 (Archival box - standard 84-8)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. May - July 1986, F-84-1-1-0-54 (Archival box - standard 84-8)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers. Oct. 1986 - Sept. 1987, 1986 - 1987; F-84-1-1-0-55 (Archival box - standard 84-8)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Nov. 1987, vol. 1, F-84-1-1-0-56 (Archival box - standard 84-8)
    - SCAP - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Nov. 1987, vol. 2, F-84-1-1-0-57 (Archival box - standard 84-8)
  - Senate Appeals Board (SAB), 1968 - 1978; F-84-1-2; 76 cm of textual records
    - SAB - historical background -- terms of reference, 1969 - 1970; F-84-1-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 84-9)
    - SAB - minutes and papers. Nov.- Dec. 1968; Jan. - June 1969, 1968 - 1969; F-84-1-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 84-9)
    - SAB - minutes and papers. July - Dec. 1969, F-84-1-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 84-9)
    - SAB - minutes and papers. Jan. - June 1970, F-84-1-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 84-9)
    - SAB - minutes and papers. July - Sept. 1970, F-84-1-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 84-9)
    - SAB - minutes and papers. Oct. 1970, F-84-1-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 84-9)
    - SAB - minutes and papers. Nov. 1970, F-84-1-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 84-9)
    - SAB - minutes and papers. Dec. 1970, F-84-1-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 84-9)
    - SAB - minutes and papers. Jan. - Apr. 1971, F-84-1-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 84-10)
    - SAB - minutes and papers. May - Aug. 1971, F-84-1-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 84-10)
    - SAB - minutes and papers. Sept. - Dec. 1971, F-84-1-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 84-10)
    - SAB - minutes and papers. Jan. - Apr. 1972, F-84-1-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 84-10)
    - SAB - minutes and papers. May - Aug. 197+I1872, 1972; F-84-1-2-0-13 (Archival box - standard 84-10)
    - SAB - minutes and papers. Sept. - Dec. 1972, F-84-1-2-0-14 (Archival box - standard 84-10)
    - SAB - minutes and papers. Jan. - mar. 1973, F-84-1-2-0-15 (Archival box - standard 84-11)
    - SAB - minutes and papers. Apr. - July 1973, F-84-1-2-0-16 (Archival box - standard 84-11)
    - SAB - minutes and papers. Aug. - Sept. 1973, F-84-1-2-0-17 (Archival box - standard 84-11)
    - SAB - minutes and papers. Oct. - Dec. 1973, F-84-1-2-0-18 (Archival box - standard 84-11)
    - SAB - minutes and papers. Jan. - Mar. 1974, F-84-1-2-0-19 (Archival box - standard 84-11)
    - SAB - minutes and papers. Apr. - Aug. 1974, F-84-1-2-0-20 (Archival box - standard 84-11)
    - SAB - minutes and papers. Sept. 1974, F-84-1-2-0-21 (Archival box - standard 84-12)
    - SAB - minutes and papers. Nov. - Dec. 1974, F-84-1-2-0-22 (Archival box - standard 84-12)
    - SAB - minutes and papers. Jan. - June 1975, F-84-1-2-0-23 (Archival box - standard 84-12)
    - SAB - minutes and papers. July - Sept. 1975, F-84-1-2-0-24 (Archival box - standard 84-12)
    - SAB - minutes and papers. Nov. - Dec. 1975, F-84-1-2-0-25 (Archival box - standard 84-12)
    - SAB - minutes and papers. Jan. - Mar. 1976, F-84-1-2-0-26 (Archival box - standard 84-12)
    - SAB - minutes and papers. Apr. - June 1976, F-84-1-2-0-27 (Archival box - standard 84-13)
    - SAB - minutes and papers. July - Sept. 1976, F-84-1-2-0-28 (Archival box - standard 84-13)
    - SAB - minutes and papers. Oct. - Dec. 1976, F-84-1-2-0-29 (Archival box - standard 84-13)
    - SAB - minutes and papers. Jan. - Apr. 1977, F-84-1-2-0-30 (Archival box - standard 84-13)
    - SAB - minutes and papers. May - June 1977, F-84-1-2-0-31 (Archival box - standard 84-13)
    - SAB - minutes and papers. Aug. - Sept. 1977, F-84-1-2-0-32 (Archival box - standard 84-13)
    - SAB - minutes and papers. Nov. - Dec. 1977, F-84-1-2-0-33 (Archival box - standard 84-14)
    - SAB - minutes and papers. Jan. - Mar. 1978, F-84-1-2-0-34 (Archival box - standard 84-14)
    - SAB - minutes and papers. Apr. - May 1978, F-84-1-2-0-35 (Archival box - standard 84-14)
    - SAB - minutes and papers. June - July 1978, F-84-1-2-0-36 (Archival box - standard 84-14)
    - SAB - minutes and papers. Aug. 1978, F-84-1-2-0-37 (Archival box - standard 84-14)
    - SAB - minutes and papers. Sept. 1978, F-84-1-2-0-38 (Archival box - standard 84-14)
    - SAB - minutes and papers. Oct. - Dec. 1978, F-84-1-2-0-39 (Archival box - standard 84-14)
  - Senate Committee on Continuing Studies (SCCS), 1973 - 1985; F-84-1-3; 25 cm of textual records
    - SCCS - Terms of Reference, 1973; F-84-1-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 84-15)
    - SCCS - agendas and minutes, 1973; F-84-1-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 84-15)
    - SCCS - Papers NCI 1-16, 1973; F-84-1-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 84-15)
    - SCCS - agendas and minutes, 1974; F-84-1-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 84-15)
    - SCCS - Papers NCI 74. 1-25, 1974; F-84-1-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 84-15)
    - SCCS - reports, 1973 - 1974; F-84-1-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 84-15)
    - SCCS - correspondence, 1973; F-84-1-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 84-15)
    - SCCS - correspondence, 1974; F-84-1-3-0-8 (Archival box - standard 84-15)
    - SCCS - agendas, minutes and papers, 1974; F-84-1-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 84-15)
    - SCCS - agendas, minutes and papers, 1975; F-84-1-3-0-10 (Archival box - standard 84-16)
    - SCCS - agendas, minutes and papers, 1976; F-84-1-3-0-11 (Archival box - standard 84-16)
    - SCCS - agendas, minutes and papers, 1977; F-84-1-3-0-12 (Archival box - standard 84-16)
    - SCCS - agendas, minutes and papers, 1978; F-84-1-3-0-13 (Archival box - standard 84-16)
    - SCCS - agendas, minutes and papers, 1979; F-84-1-3-0-14 (Archival box - standard 84-16)
    - SCCS - agendas, minutes and papers, 1980; F-84-1-3-0-15 (Archival box - standard 84-16)
    - SCCS - agendas, minutes and papers, 1981; F-84-1-3-0-16 (Archival box - standard 84-16)
    - SCCS - agendas, minutes and papers, 1982; F-84-1-3-0-17 (Archival box - standard 84-16)
    - SCCS - agendas, minutes and papers, 1983; F-84-1-3-0-18 (Archival box - standard 84-16)
    - SCCS - agendas, minutes and papers, 1984; F-84-1-3-0-19 (Archival box - standard 84-16)
    - SCCS - agendas, minutes and papers, 1985; F-84-1-3-0-20 (Archival box - standard 84-16)
  - Senate Committee on Honorary Degrees (SCHD), 1965 - 1984; F-84-1-4; 88 cm of textual records
    - SCHD - agendas, minutes and papers. Mar. 9, 1965 - Oct. 16, 1968, 1965 - 1968; F-84-1-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 84-17)
    - SCHD - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 22, 1968 - Dec. 11, 1968, F-84-1-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 84-17)
    - SCHD - agendas, minutes and papers. Jan. 9, 1970 - Mar. 19, 1971, 1970 - 1971; F-84-1-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 84-17)
    - SCHD - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 18, 1971, F-84-1-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 84-17)
    - SCHD - agendas, minutes and papers. Jan. 4, 1972, F-84-1-4-0-5 (Archival box - standard 84-17)
    - SCHD - agendas, minutes and papers. Jan.29, 1973 - Feb. 19, 1973, F-84-1-4-0-6 (Archival box - standard 84-17)
    - SCHD - agendas, minutes and papers. Jan. 9, 1974, F-84-1-4-0-7 (Archival box - standard 84-18)
    - SCHD - agendas, minutes and papers. Aug. 7, 1974 - Nov. 14, 1974, F-84-1-4-0-8 (Archival box - standard 84-18)
    - SCHD - agendas, minutes and papers. Feb. 17, 1975 - Oct. 16, 1975, F-84-1-4-0-9 (Archival box - standard 84-18)
    - SCHD - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 6, 1975, F-84-1-4-0-10 (Archival box - standard 84-18)
    - SCHD - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 13, 1975, F-84-1-4-0-11 (Archival box - standard 84-18)
    - SCHD - agendas, minutes and papers. Aug. 5, 1976, F-84-1-4-0-12 (Archival box - standard 84-18)
    - SCHD - agendas, minutes and papers. Oct. 21, 1976, F-84-1-4-0-13 (Archival box - standard 84-18)
    - SCHD - msicellaneous papers, 1976 - 1977; F-84-1-4-0-14 (Archival box - standard 84-18)
    - SCHD - agendas, minutes and papers. Aug. 4, 1977, F-84-1-4-0-15 (Archival box - standard 84-19)
    - SCHD - agendas, minutes and papers. Sept. 30, 1977, F-84-1-4-0-16 (Archival box - standard 84-19)
    - SCHD - agendas, minutes and papers. Oct. 20, 1977, F-84-1-4-0-17 (Archival box - standard 84-19)
    - SCHD - agendas, minutes and papers. Oct. 25, 1978 - Oct. 1979, 1978 - 1979; F-84-1-4-0-18 (Archival box - standard 84-19)
    - SCHD - miscellaneous papers, 1978 - 1979; F-84-1-4-0-19 (Archival box - standard 84-19)
    - SCHD - agendas, minutes and papers. Sept. 20, 1979, F-84-1-4-0-20 (Archival box - standard 84-19)
    - SCHD - agendas, minutes and papers. Oct. 18, 1979, F-84-1-4-0-21 (Archival box - standard 84-20)
    - SCHD - special meeting. Mar. 17, 1981, F-84-1-4-0-22 (Archival box - standard 84-20)
    - SCHD - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1, vol. 1, 1980 - 1981; F-84-1-4-0-23 (Archival box - standard 84-20)
    - SCHD - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2, vol. 2, 1980 - 1981; F-84-1-4-0-24 (Archival box - standard 84-20)
    - SCHD - miscellaneous papers, 1980; F-84-1-4-0-25 (Archival box - standard 84-20)
    - SCHD - Convocation correspondence, vol. 1, vol. 1, 1968 - 1974; F-84-1-4-0-26 (Archival box - small 84-21)
    - SCHD - Convocation correspondence, vol. 2, vol. 2, 1968 - 1974; F-84-1-4-0-27 (Archival box - small 84-21)
    - SCHD - Convocation correspondence, vol. 3, vol. 3, 1968 - 1974; F-84-1-4-0-28 (Archival box - small 84-21)
    - SCHD - Convocation correspondence, vol. 4, vol. 4, 1968 - 1974; F-84-1-4-0-29 (Archival box - small 84-21)
    - SCHD - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1, vol. 1, 1981 - 1982; F-84-1-4-0-30 (Archival box - standard 84-22)
    - SCHD - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2, vol. 2, 1981 - 1982; F-84-1-4-0-31 (Archival box - standard 84-22)
    - SCHD - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 3, vol. 3, 1981 - 1982; F-84-1-4-0-32 (Archival box - standard 84-22)
    - SCHD - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1, vol. 1, 1982 - 1983; F-84-1-4-0-33 (Archival box - standard 84-22)
    - SCHD - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2, vol. 2, 1982 - 1983; F-84-1-4-0-34 (Archival box - standard 84-22)
    - SCHD - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 3, vol. 3, 1982 - 1983; F-84-1-4-0-35 (Archival box - standard 84-22)
    - SCHD - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1, vol. 1, 1983 - 1984; F-84-1-4-0-36 (Archival box - standard 84-23)
    - SCHD - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2, vol. 2, 1983 - 1984; F-84-1-4-0-37 (Archival box - standard 84-23)
    - SCHD - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 3, vol. 3, 1983 - 1984; F-84-1-4-0-38 (Archival box - standard 84-23)
    - SCHD - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Sept. - Nov. 1984, vol. 1, F-84-1-4-0-39 (Archival box - standard 84-23)
    - SCHD - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Sept. - Nov. 1984, vol. 2, F-84-1-4-0-40 (Archival box - standard 84-23)
  - Senate Library Committee (SLC), 1966 - 1981; F-84-1-5; 26 cm of textual records
    - SLC - index papers 1-150, F-84-1-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 84-24)
    - SLC - Annual Report, 1968 - 1978; F-84-1-5-0-2 (Archival box - standard 84-24)
    - SLC - agenda and minutes, 1966; F-84-1-5-0-3 (Archival box - standard 84-24)
    - SLC - papers 1-25, 1966; F-84-1-5-0-4 (Archival box - standard 84-24)
    - SLC - agenda and minutes, 1967; F-84-1-5-0-5 (Archival box - standard 84-24)